Guide to the Chasen Gaver papers, 1977-1988
Gaver, Chasen papers, 1977-1988
- Series VI. Audio/Video
  - First conference calls, March 12, 1979; tr6939a
  - Lisbon 10/8/82 (side A); Tangier - Paul Bowles (side B), c. October 1982; tr6940a
  - Interview with Jim Marks 7/11/88 (side A); Warhol's "Ultraviolet" 11/11/88 (side B), July, November 1988; tr6941a
  - Dirt meeting 9/2/80 (side A); Donald's birthday party 10/80 (side B), September-October 1980; tr6942a
  - Layng's 30th birthday 9/20/86 (side A); Cravedi phone call 3/1/87 (side B), September 1986, March 1987; tr6943a
  - Talk Tape #1 - Craig and Chasen on Mykonos, tr6944a
  - Talk Tape #2 - Super paradise, tr6945a
  - Talk Tape #3 - Mykonos, tr6946a
  - "The Last Supper," Mykonos, July 11, 1986; tr6947a
  - National Public Radio, May 11, 1988; tr6948a
  - Station to Station WPFW 11/17/81 (side A); Essex Hemphill WPFW 10/3/85 (side B), November 1981, October 1985; tr6949a
  - National Public Radio, February 16, 1980; tr6950a
  - Gaver on WPFW-FM 89.3, "The poet and the poem," 7:30 pm, March 6, 1986; tr6951a-tr6953
  - Station to Station WPFW, April 1, 1982; tr6954a
  - Gaver on WAMU-FM, "Poetry with the poets," 6/19/79 (side A); WPFW, Interview, 4/20/81 (side B), June 1979, April 1981; tr6955a
  - Colevia, Cravedi, March 24-27, 1984; tr6956a
  - RAT staff 4/9/79 (side A); Boss/Wayne/Emillie/Chasen in RATS II (side B), c. March 1979; tr6857a
  - Craig/Chasen on "The Embassy," New York 6/22/79 (side A); Christopher Street docks 6/23/79 (side B), June 1979; tr6958a-6959a
  - Gideon Ferebee on WPFW, June 14, 1984; tr6960a
  - Michelle Parkerson on WPFW, July 10, 1988; tr6961a
  - Cravedi in Boston, September 1986; tr6962a
  - Dirt editorial session 3/23/79 (side A); Donald 4/23/79 (side B), March-April 1979; tr6963a
  - Craig's speech 3/28/79 (side A); Animate objects (side B), c. March 1979; tr6964a
  - "Jumping to Conclusions", tr6965a-6974a
  - WPA reading, May 14, 1979; tr6975a
  - Lambda Rising reading 6/19/86 (side A); Reagan and Nancy re: Drugs 9/14/86 (side B), June, September 1986; tr6976a
  - "Innuendo," "Impact," "Another Show Biz", tr6977a
  - "Things in 2's", tr6978a
  - "In Common", tr6979a
  - "Then What?", tr6980a
  - "I Get Around" (video soundtrack), tr6981a
  - "Stay or Go", tr6982a-6988a
  - "Opening Night", October 10, 1979; tr6989a